###### White Label
    
    ### For SaaS Platforms & Agencies
    
    Provide our complete analytics suite to your clients, directly within your own interface and with your/their own branding. Discover Analytics-as-a-Service and White Label Analytics. Great benefit, minimal effort.

    * [What Is Eco-Friendly Sustainable Marketing? \[+Strategies & Examples\]](https://www.visitor-analytics.io/en/blog/sustainable-marketing-explained "What Is Eco-Friendly Sustainable Marketing? [+Strategies & Examples]")
    * [Product-Led Growth and Marketing: Teach Your Platform to Do The Talking](https://www.visitor-analytics.io/en/blog/product-led-growth "Product-Led Growth and Marketing: Teach Your Platform to Do The Talking")

    Expand Your Knowledge

    Getting Started

    Due Diligence

[

Login as existing user](https://app.twipla.com/login?utm_campaign=visaWebsite&utm_source=headerButton&utm_term=login)

* Privacy Policy

Quick Navigation

Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Policy
--------------

In order to provide our service, we may process the personal data of you and the visitors of your website. We have therefore drawn up a data processing agreement (DPA) which describes how we carry out this processing, what our obligations are, how we keep your and your website visitors' data secure and what your obligations are as a customer. TWIPLA is a data processor for all customers (Controller) and the Data Processing Agreement constitutes the agreement of the parties with respect to the processing of personal data carried out through our service. As Controller, in order to sign this Agreement, you must review and digitally sign a copy of the Data Processing Agreement. You can find it at any time in your account by logging into TWIPLA and going to the [Privacy Center](https://www.visitor-analytics.io/en/features/website-statistics/privacy-center). You can also see the DPA content below. If you have any further questions on this topic, please do not hesitate to email us at [support@twipla.com](mailto:support@twipla.com).

Data Processing Agreement
-------------------------

We offer a very comprehensive [Data Processing Agreement (DPA)](https://www.visitor-analytics.io/en/support/legal-data-privacy-certificates/standard-integration/data-processing-agreement) which complies fully with GDPR and its requirements.

You can review our [Data Processing Agreement (DPA)](https://www.visitor-analytics.io/en/support/legal-data-privacy-certificates/standard-integration/data-processing-agreement) here with the list of our subprocessorss. Also please find a link to the [TOMs (Technical organizational measurements) of our hosting provider HETZNER](https://www.twipla.com/en/hetzner-toms).

Privacy Policy for the Google Analytics Importer
------------------------------------------------

Using the TWIPLA Google Analytics importer will import the selected data within the selected daterange for you into the TWIPLA infrastructure.  

All data will be imported into our data infrastructure in order to ensure further processing within the TWIPLA platform provided by server nodes located in Germany, provided by [HETZNER](https://www.hetzner.com/). HETZNER as our subprocessor complies with all known worldwide data privacy regulations.

We comply with the [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy) (including the Limited Use requirements).

### Do you need more help?

### Subscribe to Our Newsletter

Please insert a valid email address.

**Subscribe**

[What Is Eco-Friendly Sustainable Marketing? \[+Strategies & Examples\]](https://www.visitor-analytics.io/en/blog/sustainable-marketing-explained)

**Quicklinks**

**Company**

**Legal Information**

### Become an affiliate

Refer your customers to TWIPLA and get **a 20% commission** on their payment.

**Contact Us**

**Visitor Analytics GmbH**  
Seestraße 76  
82335 Berg  
Germany

**Visitor Analytics SRL**  
Calea Dorobantilor 18  
400117 Cluj-Napoca  
Cluj-County, Romania

© 2024 Copyright The Website Intelligence Platform. All rights reserved.
